The boat was full of weapons.
Rocket launchers. assault rifles.
Military grade. European. I think.
Who knew what was in that ship?
Only the Captain
and the First Mate.
The people I work for are very grateful
for the use of your port.
If Fisk gets the guns off the boat
into Red Hook. they disappear.
You know what to do.
He killed them all.
Fisk is tough.
He's getting in the ring this weekend.
isn't he?
Daredevil got away.
Get in!
Apparently. someone is helping him.
Someone with very good aim.
Have you ever been in the same room
with Benjamin Poindexter?
I have.
Can I help you?
Father. I...
I need absolution.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
♪ Some folks like to get away ♪
♪ Take a holiday from the neighborhood ♪
♪ Hop a flight to Miami Beach
or to Hollywood ♪
Ah. Tony.
Good morning. Mrs. Smithers.
♪ I'm in a New York state of mind ♪
Such a nice boy.
Have a nice day.
♪ I've seen all the movie stars ♪
♪ In their fancy cars
and their limousines ♪
♪ Under the evergreens ♪
♪ I know what I'm needing ♪
You ready?
What are you famous for?
I mean. the milkshakes are good.
- Excellent.
- Mm-hmm.
I'll have. uh...
one banana milkshake.
You want whip?
Doesn't everybody?
Task Force hotline.
What's your emergency?
I think I just saw Frank Castle
enter Bel Aire Diner at 43rd and 10th.
The Punisher?
Are you sure?
Oh. yeah.
Yeah. it's him.
Task force is en route.
Shit.
He has a gun.
Try to find a safe place...
There you go.
Thank you.
Entry team get prepped.
Let's do it. Let's get...
- On your six!
- On me. on me!
Everybody. stay in your seats!
- Keep your hands up!
- Hey! Hey!
- Everyone. sit down!
- Don't move!
- Nobody leaves! Nobody leaves!
- Throw 'em down!
Down!
- Let's go!
- Stay down!
- Nobody fucking move.
- You got eyes?
- I got nothin'.
- What's in the back?
- Clear!
- Max?
Clear!
Yo!
Milkshake!
Put your goddamn hands up.
Turn around now.
Let's go!
What...
- Stop resisting!
- Now!
♪ I don't have any reasons ♪
♪ I left them all behind ♪
That was a great milkshake.
Huh?
Dogs in restaurants are unsanitary.
Please don't...
kill me.
Oh. don't worry.
I'm one of the good guys.
♪ I'm just taking a Greyhound ♪
♪ On the Hudson River Line ♪
Negative.
Can we know get an...
It's fucking Bullseye!
It's Bullseye! It's...
♪ 'Cause I'm in ♪
♪ I'm in a New York ♪
♪ State of mind ♪
♪ Yeah. yeah ♪
It's me again.
A cringe explosion in the East River?
Don't worry about it!
Floating dead bodies?
Don't worry about it.
All smoke and mirrors.
distracting you from the main event!
My charity boxing match...
...that's raising money for a New York
Born Again revitalization project.
that is really a shell corporation
for money laundering
to offshore accounts
that make my friends grotesquely rich.
I've been training hard at the gym
for you. New York.
The money we will raise will go to
arresting you without due process.
seizing your property
for my personal gain.
locking up your loved ones.
and so much more.
Back to the gym. I go. because
I love you. New York!
We're getting split
by coordinates. Nothing to report.
My name is Soledad Ayala.
I am a nurse from Washington Heights.
I was arrested by the Task Force.
the same people who killed my husband.
I am the missing.
But I will not back down.
I will stay...
and fight.
It's okay. Thank you.
It's time for me to go.
I wish you'd reconsider.
I have been
in a cage for...
...six months.
I need to shower.
I need to burn these clothes.
I'm too old for this shit.
Ah. it's a shame 'cause we could use
more people like you.
Like me?
You don't realize it. do you?
You're not a hero.
You're a symbol now.
Hope for an entire city.
It's true.
I gave Karen an account number.
Use whatever you need.
whenever you need it.
Thank you.
Good luck. my friend.
Destroy them both.
- Hey.
What you got there?
Uh. SD card.
I'm supposed to get it to my source.
but with the Task Force everywhere.
- I'm too exposed.
- It's okay.
Let me do it.
- Absolutely not.
- Oh. come on.
No. come on. I just need
to do this for my aunt. please.
No way. It's too dangerous.
So what?
I stole their truck.
They're probably already
looking for me.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Do you understand the responsibility
that comes with this?
Yeah.
I do.
Are you ready?
Were you?
Everybody. stay still.
My name is Christofi Savva.
I'm here to help.
I was the First Mate on the Northern Star.
That's one way to deal with the Governor.
It's for the journey.
not the meeting.
Marge and I have a rapport.
And I appreciate you talkin' to her.
I know what you're doing.
Arranging this
trip to Albany just before the fight.
I don't like it...
when you send me away and shut me out.
This is not that.
It's a public place.
Too much could go wrong.
We're a matched set.
I should be there tonight.
I'll call you when it's over.
Good luck.
You were captured
only for helping me.
I would like to return that kindness.
What can you tell us
about the Northern Star?
Everything.
The illegal weapons. the fake documents...
Can you connect any of it to Fisk?
We were protected.
All the paperwork was signed off by...
Vasillias tou Enklimatos.
The Kingpin.
Well. we need an attorney
to take his statement.
- Kirsten...
- Yeah. yeah.
Well. it's too dangerous
to bring Christofi to her.
so she'll have to come to us.
Won't be too hard. All the Task Force
will be at the fight tonight.
Yeah. yeah.
At Fogwell's.
Some of the last memories
of my father are in that gym.
Now. it's crawling
with Task Force.
Yeah. he wants me there.
Or...
Not just me.
The whole fight...
He's setting a trap for Bullseye.
Oh. fuck.
- I'm gonna find Bullseye.
- Mm-hmm.
- You just connect Kirsten and Christofi.
- Christofi.
Yep.
- All right. Be careful.
- You. too.
I love you.
I love you. too.
I'm here outside Fogwell's Gym.
a part of Mayor Fisk's Born Again
revitalization project.
and host to tonight's benefit boxing match
between the Mayor and heavyweight
Mike "the Matterhorn" Melendez.
Due to the recent spate
of vigilante violence.
I'm told security will be tight.
with increased Task Force to...
No. I don't understand.
I was under the impression
that that account was paid in full.
Down on the fucking ground now!
Down on the fucking ground!
Out of your fucking chairs! Down!
- On the fucking ground! Down!
- Hey! Hey!
You assholes better have a warrant. or
I'm gonna bury you under so many lawsuits
that your grandchildren's grandchildren
will still be paying your legal bills.
Safer Streets.
- I don't need a warrant or probable cause.
- We won't even need to knock.
You again?
- Where's your client?
- Which one?
Terrorist fugitive Jack Duquesne.
also known as Swordsman.
- Allegedly.
- A court of law found him guilty.
That was no court.
Whatever.
I'm not gonna fucking ask you again.
Do you see him here? Anywhere?
Maybe he's hiding under a pile of files
or that wall made of glass.
Nothing. sir.
You hear from him. you turn him in.
Attorney-client privilege still applies.
I don't give a fuck about your
attorney-client whatever the fuck.
He was part of a terrorist attack
that killed 25 men
- on board that ship.
- Bullshit.
Talk like that will get you hurt someday.
Talk like that is how I do my fucking job.
You tell Matt Murdock we said hello. Okay?
See you around. Counselor!
First. Bullseye and now this.
And how many escaped?
Nineteen in total.
I've had enough!
There's leaks in Red Hook.
leaks in City Hall!
You need to find them. Buck!
Plug them!
Every one!
- How much you wanna know?
- Enough to know what's...
You know what I wanna know?
Why...
...is wombat shit cube-shaped?
I mean. it's the strangest thing
I've ever seen.
Apparently. they like to
stack it into. like.
little walls that mark
their territory.
Isn't that weird?
Little Lego walls of wombat shit
to get the bitches.
They literally shit bricks.
Charles. you are not on my agenda.
I have another awesome
existential question.
Why is my non-cube shitting ass
sitting on a pile of HK 416s
and rocket launchers.
and other assorted weapons. when this.
all of this. is not supposed to be
in a warehouse in Brooklyn.
It's supposed to be on its way to
Guinea-Bissau to win the hearts and minds.
Because Daredevil knows it's in New York.
People need these arms.
Shots must be fired.
If you put these on another boat.
we'll have the Northern Star
all over again. or worse.
And I don't need my city
turning on me. Not now.
Your city.
- That's rich.
- Do not mock me!
It is a big world out there. sailor.
With big wars and much. much bigger stakes
than one elected official.
Official who gave you access
to an American free port.
And on behalf of the agency.
we appreciate your service.
A service. I might remind you.
which is yet to be rendered.
I will honor our arrangement.
Well. that's great.
I mean. the question kind of becomes
"Can you?" Right?
I mean. you've been rocking and rolling
with all your big cat friends.
And then Uncle Sam shows up.
and your facility. the...
the golden fucking goose is cooked
because this place is compromised.
And your Governor is threatening
to revoke its charter.
You are overreaching.
From where I'm sitting.
it seems to me you're having a...
Just a very difficult time
controlling...
your very. very small piece of the world.
I am not your employee!
I never said you were.
Partners. Wilson...
Come on! We're partners.
Hey. I don't respond well to threats.
That's not a threat.
Look. neither of us ever walk in anywhere
without knowing how we're gonna get out.
It's adorable.
but you can put your hands down.
You're right.
Your shipment will be delivered
when the time is right.
I would ask that you practice patience!
Next time you wanna see me. call.
It's courteous.
Shit.
This was retaliation.
and then our accounts
are mysteriously frozen.
It's not a coincidence.
I wouldn't be here if it wasn't important.
Yeah. Well. the last time I helped you.
I ended up as an accessory
to a terrorist attack.
Well. and Fisk sunk that ship.
Not Daredevil.
Where's Matt?
Karen?
Can't answer that...
but he's safe.
Okay.
You think you know people...
Here.
Thanks.
You do. you know.
All right.
What do you need? And how much
is it gonna screw with my life?
To be honest.
I was expecting the call.
I just wasn't expecting it from you.
It's not often I'm surprised.
You and I speak
a more similar language than my husband.
The Mayor. I understand.
It's you. that's the mystery to me.
Now. he... he's like the White Bull.
crashing through everything.
Does that make you Europa?
Oh. I'm no victim.
I'm not entirely sure she was either.
We can be candid
with each other. right?
Of course. that's why I'm here.
I don't like the way your husband
wields his power.
I don't trust it.
and it makes me nervous.
I don't see Safer Streets.
a thriving economy. and...
neighborhood revitalization as problems.
"New York Born Again."
A bit grandiose. don't you think?
My husband has big plans
for the city he loves.
It'd be a shame if New York's progress
was halted because of
unfortunate decisions.
I said the Mayor gives me pause.
You don't.
The city shuts down businesses.
you unload them to Cooper and others.
laying down the infrastructure
for long-term growth.
It's shrewd...
and ruthless.
And I mean that as a compliment.
I take it as one.
Thank you.
You could have done all of this
on your own.
And yet. you chose to do it with Wilson.
Why?
I never thought it'd be him.
And then it was.
And now I can't imagine it...
being any other way.
Can you temper his darker impulses?
You want guarantees that I can't give you.
but I can give you this...
my husband loves New York.
and I love my husband.
And I know how to bring out
the very best in him.
Honestly. I... I couldn't sleep at night
backing Mayor Fisk.
But I can back Mayor and Mrs. Fisk.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Uh. we ran out of guac. bro.
but shit's still gonna be bussin'.
Uh. welcome to Arriba Arepas.
What do you want?
Una arepa paisa. por favor.
Oh. my gosh. A leprechaun.
- Did you lose your pot of gold?
- Just shut the fuck up. Javi.
I need you to do something for me.
Fuck is this?
I need you not to screw it up.
Chill. I got you.
I will seriously beat your ass.
Ay. ay!
You don't want that arepa?
I... I guess not.
Yeah. I'm not taking customers right now.
Give me one second.
All right. wrap it up! Let's go.
Get lost!
CSI's not done.
Vigilante crimes. Task Force jurisdiction.
What. are you pulling rank?
Let's go!
Want me to call my friends?
Hate these Task Force pricks.
Jesus Christ.
"Saint Lucia.
"your beautiful name signifies light.
"By the light of the faith
that God bestowed upon you...
"increase and preserve this light
in my soul so that I may avoid evil.
"be zealous in the performance
of good works...
"And abhor nothing so much
as the darkness of evil and sin.
"Amen."
Haven't heard
that one in a long time.
I. uh...
I knew a boy.
Uh. he was blind.
Saint Lucia got him through
some tough times.
You seem troubled. officer.
Actually. I... I. uh.
grew up in this church.
Haven't been back in a minute.
Tell me. what...
What brings you back?
I found that at a murder scene today.
These tokens are available
to all our parishioners.
So I couldn't possibly know who left this.
Tell me who you think...
left it.
There was a man.
He came looking for a nun
who used to be assigned here.
This man...
uh. what did he want?
He came looking for. um...
I... I don't know.
Counsel. Penance.
I told him
I wasn't a priest yet...
He held a knife on me.
And what did he say?
Listen to me...
This man...
is a killer.
Even so. I can't turn someone over
to the police.
His judgment is not for us to say.
Yeah. I'm not gonna debate with you
whether or not he deserves grace...
but I do need to find him.
or others will die.
What will you do...
when you find him?
I won't kill him.
He told me he wakes every morning
to the sound of the church bells.
And he watches me open the doors
for morning mass.
Watches from where?
His window.
Let me help you with that.
See you tomorrow.
Such a nice boy.
I'm on your side.
What are you doing to my Tony?
Stop!
One good deed!
Put the gun down!
What I did...
- What that woman had me do...
- No. no. no. no. no.
- ...to your friend...
- Don't you bring him up!
Don't you dare bring him up!
Not like this!
But I had to get out.
I had to get my mind back.
And one good deed.
it levels the scales again.
Oh! Uh...
- All right. Okay.
- No!
What is the. uh...
What is this. uh. one good deed?
What is it you wanna do?
What you wouldn't do.
What you won't do.
I can't...
I can't let you make a martyr out of him.
I'm gonna make things right.
I'm gonna help you.
Please. Look. just calm down.
I am calm.
My name
is Christofi Savva.
I was the First Mate on the Northern Star.
My Captain. Achilleo Kyriacou.
scuttled the ship.
We were under orders to sink the ship
if it was ever boarded.
Why was that?
Because the Northern Star
was carrying weapons.
military grade. very illegal.
And who was the one
who ordered you to scuttle the ship?
Achilleo called him...
Vasillias tou Enklimatos.
the Kingpin...
but we knew it was the Mayor.
There was no customs check.
We did not have to present
a bill of lading or manifest.
We were never registered with Coast Guard.
Homeland Security. none of it.
I've been to many ports
all over this world.
In order to make that happen...
you have to own the city.
Uh. "own the city" is correct?
Yeah. in this case. it just might be.
You said you were under orders
to scuttle the Northern Star
if it was boarded.
Who boarded the vessel?
Coast Guard?
Uh. no.
One man.
Daredevil.
The marshals are on their way.
They'll keep you safe.
Hello.
Look at that.
Ringside. baby.
We're gonna be so close. you and me.
that we're gonna be
covered in sweat tonight.
That didn't come out
how it sounded in your head.
Did not. You know what? I was saying it.
and I sort of realized
as it was coming out that
it wasn't really what I meant.
- So. uh...
- Mm.
Anyways. um...
thank you for inviting me.
Of course.
Yo! You're BB.
Like The BB Report.
Yeah. that... that's me. You watch that?
Everybody watches it.
My brother. my cousin. my tía.
Yo. they're obsessed.
Oh. can I get a pic?
It's gonna blow their mind.
Yeah. for sure. Come on.
Yo. appreciate you.
My bad.
Didn't realize
I was on a date with a celebrity.
Come on.
I'm not a celebrity and not a date.
Yeah. not yet.
Make a fist.
- Feel good?
- Yeah.
Uh. that's not necessary.
He'll never lay a glove on me.
I like
your style. Mayor.
Anything?
No. We have men on rooftops. subways.
every entrance. and exit.
Inside's covered. too.
We have Task Force in plainclothes
and uniforms lugging serious firepower.
so nothing's getting in.
We'll need an entrance cleared.
Preferably. the front doors.
Sir. uh. I don't think tying yourself
to the stake is a very...
...good idea.
Looks like
you have somewhere to be.
I'm not going anywhere...
especially if you wanna
dangle yourself out as bait.
Buck...
go.
We can't have any loose ends.
Don't worry. sir. Me and North got it.
♪ I was working.
I couldn't understand it ♪
♪ I was hurting. I was in a panic ♪
♪ See. I felt like
I ain't meet the standards ♪
♪ But yet. I made it at a disadvantage ♪
♪ Yes. I made it at a disadvantage ♪
- All right. I got prezzies.
- Ooh.
I thought you're a foam finger kinda lady.
I'm not.
And there you go.
Oh. Thank you.
Look at this.
Bobblehead Fisk. uh?
Very realistic.
Look at that.
Pure class.
I hope you got the discount.
There's a discount?
Shit.
Ladies and gentlemen.
proud New Yorkers.
welcome to Scrappin' In The Kitchen.
benefiting the New York Born Again
revitalization project.
The main event
will consist of three rounds.
Winner determined by knockout.
TKO. or points.
Now. get out of your seats.
clap your hands. and welcome...
In purple trunks.
weighing in at 235 pounds
with a professional record
of thirty-two and two.
Mike "The Matterhorn" Melendez!
And in the white corner.
our hometown hero of Hell's Kitchen.
wearing white trunks.
weighing in at 325 pounds.
with no professional boxing record.
Mayor Wilson "Wildcard" Fisk!
- Yeah!
- Boo!
- Yeah! Fisk! Fisk! Fisk!
Fisk! Fisk! Fisk! Fisk!
Fisk!
I want a clean fight.
Nothing below the belt.
Obey my commands.
Defend yourselves at all times.
Touch gloves.
Yeah!
Yeah! Yes!
Let's go!
That what you want? Fine!
Hello. Mr. Savva.
- Yeah! Yes! Yes!
- Oh. my God.
Christofi's been taken care of.
All right.
Yeah!
Oh!
Oh. my God.
You came.
With a win.
- I told you not to come.
- Kiss me.
Listen to me.
Kiss me.
You need to go now.
Get her out of here!
Get out of the way. Get down.
Let me go!
Get her out of here now!
Shoot him down!
Get her out of here!
Get her out!
Go get them!
Now!
Fifteen. Let's go! Let's go!
Wilson...
Get an ambulance!
Somebody. please!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm